A skeleton dating 200 years back
found in the Himalayas,
matched with the DNA
of his missing step-sister.
I managed to find an email
Professor Ishimizaki sent to Kayoko Senba.
Shiharu is involved in this sin of his.
This is...
Even if you managed to find your sister,
I would simply devour her.
Sir.
Your visitor has arrived.
Let her through.
Good evening. To what do I owe the pleasure?
Can you not even monitor your own son?
I see.
So he visited you.
Don't "I see" me.
You killed Ishimizaki, did you not?
I did.
And you...
are my accomplice.
I had no hand in his death.
What are you accusing me of?
We practically killed the man ourselves.
You had ambition.
I had my reasons.
Ishimizaki was only caught in the crossfire.
[27 Years Ago]
Doctor.
I found something very interesting.
See?
This is in very good condition.
And there is still muscle fiber that remains.
Thank you.
We'll use this, Nanase.
Understood.
Ishimizaki, get the box ready.
These bones are in great condition.
Finally, we can begin.
[Haruka Nanase]
Haruka, where are you right now?
Are you trying to get rid of me?
What?
I was nearly killed.
What? Are you hurt?
I was burnt.
He poured some sort of chemical on me.
If he doused me in it, I'd be dead.
Where are you? Are you safe?
I'll send someone to get you.
You're the one after my neck!
I'm not, I swear it.
Tell me, what happened?
You tried to get me admitted to a ward.
I heard.
The doctor deemed it was best for you.
Really, the doctor?
I know it was your plan all along.
You think the doctor was acting on my orders?
And now you're trying to kill me instead.
Calm down. There's been a misunderstanding.
Tell me where you are.
You're in grave danger right now.
That's your fault.
I'm telling you, you misunderstand.
Tell that to the man named Ushio.
I know he also killed Professor Ishimizaki.
I would never do anything to hurt you.
It's true, so please.
Tell me where you are.
Like hell I could trust you.
What are you trying to hide?
Is Shiharu somehow involved?
There's still something you don't know.
And what is that?
I'll tell you in person.
No. Tell me, now.
I can't.
Let's talk, face-to-face.
I'd rather not.
Failed to convince your son?
Silence!
If only you weren't so involved
with Plantae...
Excuse me?
You're the one with deep ties to Plantae.
This all stemmed from a plan
of your father's.
And now that it's failed,
you're trying to forget it.
As if I could so readily accept that.
Don't act like you alone are so righteous.
Your son. He's getting in your way, isn't he?
Of course not.
You must hurry
and erase all traces of "log.0".
Haruka Nanase was reported
for breaking and entering, right?
Yes, sir. Kayoko Senba made the call.
I see.
She also attended Ishimizaki's funeral.
So I heard.
Maybe Haruka Nanase
is looking into Ishimizaki's case.
You think he suspects Kayoko Senba?
There's still something he hasn't told us.
What about our other victim, Onodera?
What was he up to
before investigating Nichie?
Probably blackmail.
Blackmail?
He'd find disputes caused by minor companies
and hold it against them.
Money trouble, illegal subsidies, the works.
Then he'd make them pay up
in exchange for his silence.
Why was a man like him
pestering a major corporation
like Nichie Pharmaceutical?
What happened to your leg?
A man splashed chemicals onto it.
What? Who?
The bastard who attended
Kayoko Senba's lecture.
- The police...
- Forget them. What did you find?
- But...
- Just tell me.
I found this old article.
Roopkund?
Look here.
That's...
My uncle, your father,
and Kayoko Senba were at Roopkund.
Have you heard of Roopkund?
I believe so.
I wonder what it is they were investigating.
I'll go see Kayoko Senba.
You should leave. It'll be dangerous.
We ought to report this.
The police suspect me.
I want to talk to Kayoko Senba
before I'm caught.
I'll come with you.
Something began at that cursed lake.
[The bones from two centuries ago
and his missing step-sister]
I heard Kayoko Senba visited.
[log.4]
- Was there any trouble?
- No.
Not at all.
What of our applied technology center?
Proceed with the demolitions.
And please, make it quick.
Yes, sir.
See her to a meeting room.
Kasuga's here.
Can you handle her?
Yes, sir.
Is the President not available?
I have been entrusted
to handle these matters myself.
Is that so.
Why have I been called here today?
We wanted to confirm every last trace
of "log.0" has been done away with.
I believe we got rid of everything back then.
We ask that you be absolutely certain.
None of our records remain
in your files either, yes?
But of course.
I ask that you be absolutely certain of it.
I've sacrificed my family for this.
I cannot afford to trouble them any further.
We shall bring you no trouble.
Good.
I will leave after sitting for a bit.
Please take your time.
Maehara! I'm glad we caught you.
We have a few questions.
A reporter came to visit Mr. Nanase
the other day, yes?
His name was "Onodera". Ring a bell?
Yes. What about him?
He was found as a pile of bones.
We're obviously trying to figure out why.
Mind helping us out?
Of course.
Onodera's come to visit Nichie recently.
This footage is from the garage here.
Yes, and what of it?
He's acting pretty persistent.
What sort of questions did he ask?
I'm sorry, but I cannot disclose
information regarding the business.
Would we need a warrant?
I cannot say much else about it.
Where are you headed off to?
I'm being sent to a hospital
to deal with prescriptions.
Mr. Kyoichi treats me
like an errand boy, at best.
There were officers in your lobby just now.
Maehara is speaking to them.
Worry not. The police know nothing.
And you're certain nothing will leak
from your side of things?
I have erased all evidence of "log.0".
Did you have Ushio "erase"
the now dead reporter as well?
Nanase.
What are you planning to do with Ushio?
[Member of the Lower House, 32nd District]
You're certainly absorbed in your work.
Chief...
The higher-ups told me
to check on my underlings.
Are you getting up to something?
Just doing my job, sir.
You're no rookie, bud.
I know.
Careful, or you'll step on a landmine.
Yeah, I know politics
and finance can get dicey...
Right. Don't mess with the wrong gang.
Sorry, Chief. I got to get going.
Talk to you later.
Sorry!
[Yoko Kasuga]
[Chief of PR]
- Are you alright?
- Yeah.
You really ought to leave this case.
So you say.
It's dangerous to get more involved.
I know.
But I can't back off now.
If you die, who will be there
when Mari returns?
Then will you call it quits here?
Of course not.
And neither will I.
I'm eternally grateful to Mari.
I was never able to fit in.
At school, my jobs, wherever.
I'm surprised to hear that. Were you bullied?
Not exactly.
How should I put it...
You probably realize by now
I'm honest to a fault, right?
So I struggled to join other girls
in their superficial conversations.
They would just... slowly shun me.
But I could always tell Mari anything.
She'd tell me everything, too.
She's the reason I'm the person I am now.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
You haven't been skipping school these days.
Well, university is no high school.
It actually offers me a place to study.
How is university different from high school?
Let's see...
No one makes fun of me for eating alone,
or other silly things like that, for one.
Why would they anyway?
Middle and high school
were full of confusing rules like that.
And university is better?
Way better.
I see.
We hung out more
when you were in high school.
Now you bring your work here.
I can't avoid doing homework.
I used to be able to tell you anything.
You'd tell me everything, too.
I still can.
- Really?
- Watch.
Today for lunch, I had ginger pork.
The special was the grilled chicken, but...
I wasn't asking about your lunch.
What were you up to today?
I was at home all day.
I see.
Should we go inside?
Yeah.
You forgot your tea.
Whoops! Thanks.
I got your meal, Tada.
Thanks.
The cheap stuff, again?
You only gave me 1,000 yen
for both our meals and drinks.
What'd you get?
- That looks good.
- I'm not sharing.
It's pretty good.
What did you think of Maehara?
Right, Nichie's errand boy.
He's a direct subordinate to the President.
According to Team Two,
Maehara's always been doing shady work.
What, he deals with bribes?
Most likely.
Pharmaceuticals are always competing
to create the newest drug.
He was probably in charge of buy outs, too.
I see.
That guy was pursuing baseball in college,
until a certain scandal broke out.
One of his teammates claimed
an upperclassman was abusing him.
Maehara wasn't directly involved,
but the incident ruined his career.
He was treated the same
as those who were guilty.
No company hired him,
until the Nichie President took him in.
So that's why Maehara can't go against him?
Yeah, he feels indebted to the guy.
Was anyone scheduled to visit?
No.
[Nichie Pharmaceutical Applied Tech Center]
Run!
Wait!
Maehara, who were those men?
They're most likely with Xin Ming Ah.
Get rid of all other paper evidence.
Yes, sir.
The man who arrived was with Nichie.
To visit a defunct lab... How strange.
There was definitely something there
they didn't want us finding.
All forces, listen up!
We got a witness report of Haruka Nanase.
Got you now, Haruka Nanase.
He was last seen at Terano Shopping Street.
We're rolling out.
Yes, sir.
Once we question Kayoko Senba,
let's return to the Professor's place.
Do you think we can get inside?
Yes. I have the keys.
He may have a clue regarding Roopkund.
Something the police missed.
Right.
- Let's go.
- Huh?
Hey, wait! Haruka Nanase!
Mayuzumi, take the car and ambush them!
Yes, sir!
What now?
Will you come with us to the station,
Haruka Nanase?
Murderer!
That man's a murderer! Run!
Folks, please!
Calm down!
Excuse me, let me through!
He has a dangerous chemical! Watch out!
Police!
What happened?
You're coming with us.
[The Plantae Gathering]
All who suffer must offer
their flesh and blood
to quench thy thirst.
All who suffer must offer
their flesh and blood
to quench thy thirst.
All sacrifice will one day
return to your body.
Like Plantae, who bear fruit
and flourish in rain.
Rain does not choose the dry.
It supplies to all.
Water climbs the heavens,
till it returns to Earth.
All manners occur in an eternal cycle.
And we exist, as a part of this eternity.
Haruka Nanase was attacked by Ushio.
What?
Contact the President of Nichie right away.
Yes, ma'am.
The new medicine has been
developed without issue.
- Approvals are soon to be filed.
- Good.
[J]
- As for when...
- Pardon me.
Hello?
Is he hurt?
I see.
Who was that man?
I don't know.
He called himself "Ushio".
Ushio.
Did he say anything else?
Excuse me.
If my father asks to speak with me,
please do not let him through.
He may have sent that man after me.
Your own father?
What makes you say that?
I am searching for my missing sister.
A sister...
Can I get her name?
Her name is Shiharu Nanase.
Haruka Nanase. Can I confirm something?
Yes, sir.
Did you visit a Furukawa Clinic
the other day?
Yes, sir.
The director there is saying you ran amok,
and injured one of their nurses.
Is that true?
Since they filed a report,
I'll have to ask about that, too.
My father tried to forcibly have me admitted.
I only acted in self defense.
Let's get our stories straight.
First of all.
Why'd you break into Kayoko Senba's home?
They suspect he's manipulating the market.
So that's why surveillance is on his ass.
I heard the Nichie stock is about to tank.
Can anyone tell me more?
Nichie? Their stock won't tank or rise.
But I heard there was trouble
with the previous head?
Oh yeah, wasn't someone looking into them?
What was his name...
Right, Hirama. From Toho Journal.
Can you introduce me to him?
He's actually here right now.
Do you know anyone in Plantae?
I want a lead, without our Chief finding out.
Well...
Mr. Hirama from Toho Journal, yes?
Did you know a reporter
by the name of Onodera?
Give us a minute.
Yes, sir.
And try to find someone, will you?
Yeah, yeah.
He came to me with questions
just the other day.
[Yoichi Onodera]
He wanted to ask about Nichie Pharmaceutical.
What was Onodera looking into?
Onodera mentioned the "Plantae" to me.
I work as the Japanese representative
for Xin Ming Ah, a Chinese conglomerate.
The name is Kojima.
I look into Japanese companies
Xin Ming Ah wishes to buy out.
I see.
So you plan to purchase
Nichie Pharmaceutical.
That was the plan.
But we are currently at a standstill.
Why is that?
Share with me whatever you know.
And I will offer my intel to you.
Why hasn't the buy out occurred yet?
There was a suspicious exchange of money.
We first visited Nichie last month.
We, Xin Ming Ah, plan to buy out
Nichie Pharmaceutical.
Bring up the other matter as well.
However, we have refrained
from taking action after noticing
a discrepancy in your financial statements.
Your budget for developing medicines
increases during a certain period of time.
Impossible.
I've brought the result
of my investigation right here.
You there.
Bring these to your President.
Shall I help? I know they are heavy.
Sir.
I see.
These are documents
from my father's time as President.
Indeed.
I understand.
We shall look into it,
and reach out again after some discussion.
Please do.
Since reporting our findings,
they've begun to make an effort
to get rid of all associated evidence.
A buy out would bring their secrets to light.
I suppose that was their biggest fear.
Indeed.
Then Nichie Pharmaceutical
is hiding something after all.
This is the last of it.
If you find anything else, dispose it,
or hand the data directly to me.
Do not send it over in any way.
Yes, sir.
Hello?
Right now?
Your father requested I deliver you
a change of clothes, and other necessities.
You will find them with the receptionist.
Is that all?
Your father worries about you.
Please do not come again.
I do not need any more "necessities".
Is that so.
Why were you attacked?
That's none of your business.
Are you looking into the missing bones?
Do they interest you?
No, rather...
Your father, he worries for you.
I know he had Dr. Furukawa
file a complaint.
Why would he do that?
To keep me shackled here.
He doesn't want me looking into those bones.
Why don't you accept your father's help,
and have him give you a job?
He almost killed me.
Your father is worried Professor Ishimizaki
got you involved in some trouble.
He said you were in danger.
And now you have been attacked.
How is any of that your father's fault?
To me, it seems you alone
are creating a fuss out of nothing.
You are blessed, you know that?
Think back to your life
before your mother remarried.
What do you know about me?
I grew up with similar circumstances.
I have killed my own desires
to claw my way to this position.
Yet my orders are
to bring you a change of clothes.
You hit the jackpot
thanks to your parents' remarriage.
You have people bringing you things,
despite the trouble you've caused.
You'd be a fool to discard
the hand you've been dealt.
If you need anything, call me.
I can't trust my father.
He's hiding something big from me.
Is that so.
This is Kasuga, speaking.
I hope you are faring well.
Did you tell Haruka Nanase anything?
You wouldn't speak of "log.0", would you?
And can I be absolutely certain?
Me, speak of that?
No, of course not.
Why would you even ask?
I believe I met every demand you asked me of.
If you find any issues,
I ask that you deal with it yourselves.
Get in.
Shiharu.
You can't leave without telling anyone.
We're going home.
Why?
They look like they're having so much fun.
Dad doesn't want you wandering around.
Come on, let's go.
I was chased out the house.
You idiot. Let me tell you.
You weren't chased out
'cause you're a stupid drunk.
Again?
I'm going to get closer.
Don't.
Shiharu.
- I'll open it.
- No, I will.
Woah!
Careful now...
Thanks, miss.
Why don't you join us?
Yeah, come here.
What were you all talking about?
Hear this! Apparently this guy
hates herring roe.
I don't like it either.
See? I have an ally.
You've just never had the real thing.
- Exactly.
- Well, I don't care.
This girl's got the right idea.
I know.
But real herring roe's delicious.
You just haven't tried the right thing.
I'll buy some next time.
The salted stuff.
It's good. Sweet, too.
Really?
They gotta be in the right condition.
You split the belly,
and out pops the roe!
It pops right out!
It's quiet.
Maybe today's not a drinking day.
No.
Some people are just made to never exist.
No one cares if they disappear.
That's an awful thing to say.
I wasn't talking about those men.
They've got questions for you.
Follow me.
Were you able to sleep?
First, I wish to speak in regards
to Professor Ishimizaki's daughter.
Mari? Has she been found?
Yes, well...
She was taken in by relatives
right after Professor Ishimizaki's passing.
She is safe.
I was told she went missing.
I have one more thing to tell you.
Please do not panic when I say this.
Your younger sister, Shiharu Nanase,
does not exist.
She died?
- No.
- Where?
Why?
Why did she die?
- Tell me, please!
- Calm down!
According to our findings,
you never had a younger sister.
What?
She never existed in the first place.
What are you talking about?
Your father has confirmed it.
We checked your family register as well.
No woman named Shiharu Nanase existed.
What are you talking about?